JAMISON BOYD

Crossville, TN • 9317435362 • jamisontboyd@gmail.com

JUNIOR LEVEL GAME DEVELOPER

25 year old Software Engineer with specialization in Virtual Reality Development and Project Management. Experience from work, education, and self-motivation learning totaling 7 years of experience.

Focused on creating an optimized and efficient workflow to deliver industry level code and documentation.

Work Experience

eCommerce Clerk

08/2022 to Present

Kroger Co

Cookeville, TN

eCommerce Clerk - Handle and deliver transactions for the eCommerce department.

 Built a prototype for Training Simulator, to create an interactive and immersive training experience for new employees for an efficient training technique.

VR Developer and Project Manager

05/2019 to 05/2022

iCube, Tennessee Technological Unversity Cookeville, TN

Virtual Reality Developer

- Programmer on "The Drop Off" Rhythm based VR game, OVR Controller, Note Generation System
- Programmer on "Impairment Arcade" Arcade game simulator, implemented 3 mini games and reward system
- Programmer on "Impairment Arcade 2D" 2D mobile arcade game simulator, implemented 6 mini games.

Project Manager

As a Project Manager, I implemented Agile, Sprint, and Scrum methods and practices, which increased the efficiency of our teams allowing us to release three projects in one year and have a fourth ready for release the semester after my graduation. These practices encouraged teamwork, communication, and motivated everyone to complete their tasks every iteration.

Experience

President

05/2019 to 06/2020

Tennessee Tech Esports Club

Cookeville, TN

President of the largest non-SGA club on campus, with over **450** members during term.

- Director of TechLAN, the largest in attendance in-person tournament held on campus, with over 200 participants in 2019.
- Held weekly meetings to encourage socializing, teamwork, and organize competitive teams to compete in sponsored tournaments for scholarships prize earnings.
- Multiple Top 8 National Placements in Nationals, Top 3 in Collegiate Worlds Championships, 1st Place in VOLAN.

Education

Tennessee Technological University

Bachelor's Computer Science Cookeville, TN 08/2017 to 05/2022

Certifications / Licenses

Responsive Web Design

02/2023

Online Certification, FreeCodeCamp.org, Certified in Responsive Web Design for HTML/CSS.

Skills

Game Engine Proficiency (Unity, Unreal Engine, Game Maker Studio)

Programming Language Proficiency (C#, C++, JavaScript, Python)

 $\textbf{Project Management} \ (\textbf{Technical documentation and communication, Collaboration and teamwork, Problem-solving and Communication, Collaboration, Collab$

and critical thinking, Time management and organization, Adaptability and ability to learn new technologies)

Cross Platform Development

Controller Remapping Support

Virtual Reality (VR) and Augmented Reality (AR) Development